It's a staple in every wardrobe a classy good-fitting catsuit and I'm going to
show you two of them today a red one and a black one by Noir Handmade I got both
of them on Amazon and they're pretty affordable so you pay between 50 and 100
euro depending on the offer you find I paid around 60 bucks and of course I'll
put the links in the description text but I'm going to get into this one now
so
that is the plain version but i'm going to add a harness on top of it
because I finally got a red one to match red catsuits. Now I just have to detangle it as always.
Yeah I think it's close enough collarmage.
I love a simple harness to elevate the whole outfit and seriously this was like
my box from Amazon too so there is a really good and rather affordable option for such an outfit
again check these out and this is the production product picture from No Handmade
I think she looks great in it but what do you think who looks better just leave a comment
this is size small and I always wear size small by No Handmade because it fits really good and
It's also long enough. I'm 173 centimeters tall and I think the arms are really long, the legs are really long, the overall body length is really long.
And I can also close this zipper without having problems here in the neck area.
So this is the closed look.
This suit is somehow giving Britney Spears vibes and I just love it.
A thing though I noticed in my comments, a lot of men tend to write me that they love women wearing these outfits.
But they do not feel confident enough to talk to women wearing these outfits
And that's why I'm excited to have the wing girl method as the sponsor of today's video
Founded by renowned dating expert and fellow youtuber Marnie, your personal wing girl
Whose channel has grown over 1.4 million subscribers as well as being featured on MTV, Dr. Drew, Ask Man and Penthouse
Her goal is to help improve the dating lives of men
But let's be honest, some guys just suck at flirting and that's where Marnie comes in.
She has helped ten thousands of men transform their dating lives with her science-backed flirting method,
the F-Formula, which has been used by a lot of men worldwide.
This proven system helps you attract the women you want and build your confidence.
This isn't for guys who are content with being alone forever,
it's for those ready to break free from their flirting failures and finally date the women they deserve.
If you're not taking action now, you're just setting yourself up to be left behind
while others grab the opportunities you're too scared to go after.
Even if you think a girl is out of your league or not interested, this step-by-step formula
can change that.
It shows you exactly how to make any woman eager to escalate with you, date you, sleep
with you and be with you.
No need to look like a model or have millions in your bank account.
With the F-formula, those things are necessary.
this method and you'll start seeing results almost immediately. Why trust
Monnie's F-Formula? Over 100,000 men have already experienced life-changing
results. This is your chance to date like the top 10% of men. And because the
Wingirl method is sponsoring today's video they're offering you an unbeatable
deal. Just click the first link in the description now and grab your exclusive
preview of the F-Formula completely for free. Plus if you decide to pick up the
program you'll get an extra 50% off. So if you're tired of failing at flirting
and being stuck on the sidelines stop wasting time. Take control of your dating
life click the link below and get access right now. In my opinion it's great that
Marnie is a woman giving advice out to men instead of just another guy telling
them what to do. She knows what women want and I know that I want to change
outfit now and get into the black catsuit so let's do that
All right, the design is slightly different.
We have this corset look-alike part here with the fake boning and also the string part.
I love that the underbust seams really sit under the boobs.
So not here.
So it's not too short.
It's actually long enough for me, which is not something that common.
And closing it still looks good.
Kind of really like this design feature here with the decorative seams.
And also long arms, long legs.
why I love my handmade catsuits. They always fit so good. There's a three-way zipper that is running
through the crotch until the back area so it's really easy to for example go to the toilet or
do other fun stuff and as you've just seen dressing is really easy and really fast because
the fabric is really smooth and slippery so undressing is even faster because that's why
people always ask how long do you need to get out of it like really fast because undressing is always
faster than dressing and dressing is already fast and there's a zipper in the crotch area so
no worries speaking of zippers we also have this nice special design feature zipper somehow because
it looks like an invisible zipper it fits seamlessly into the look of the
fabric also another point I think is quite cool so it's not like oh look at
it this is zipper no it's hidden now I mostly tend to wear pumps under catsuits
but let's try an over-kneed look
Don't worry, I'm just wearing them for a few minutes so I will wear them without socks.
Even if that bothers you.
Alright.
And I decided to do a glitter look because black and silver sparkling stuff is always a good idea.
So I have these bands which I can put on top here.
I have a choker with glitter
so this is from
Bettel von Stein and I love
how easy it is
to dress with the snaps
and I do have another glitter
accessory
this is a really cool purse
so here we are
how funny is
that handbag
like a silver cannonball
clutch. It's probably and totally in line with the choker and the boot band. I also like the
ovany look with the catsuit I have to say. Works as well. Nice. Alright that's
it for today. Don't forget to check out the wing girl method and the link in the
description down below. I hope you liked this video and the looks. Check out the
the suits on Amazon. I put the link down in the description text as well. And I will see
you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!